

CONTACT

- 09277698136
- ✓ akosianok@gmail.com
- tejero, villagonzalo 1 cebu city

EDUCATION

2014 - 2017

CEBU TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY - MAIN CAMPUS

 BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION AND COMMUNICATION TECHNOLOGY

2012 - 2014

DON SERGIO OSMENA MEMORIAL NATIONAL HIGH SCHOOL

2008 - 2009 TEJERO ELEMENTARY SCHOOL

SKILLS

- CSS, HTML and Javascript
- Wordpress
- Basic SEO
- Knowledge in Responsive Design (more on grid system)
- Photoshop
- MS office
- E-commerce data entry
- Basic React.js
- Video Editing

LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Tagalog

WESSON ENRIQUEZ

WEB DEVELOPER/DATA ENTRY

PROFILE

I have been working as a web developer for 5 years till now. I believe I am a very ambitious person who loves to work on making the website work well. Working on the web is my passion as I love to work on exciting projects and I'm excited also to bring my analytical skills to a new company and continue to make data-driven decisions. I'm able to present data in a clear and understandable way to both technical and non-technical stakeholders.

WORK EXPERIENCE

- Cybertech Corporation Research and Development Center 2020 PRESENT Software Developer
 - Create, modify and fix japanese website
 - Manage latest trend in responsive web design.
 - Monitor the consistency of code structure for future updates.

Cyscorpions Inc.

Web Developer

- Create and manage japanese website.
- Oversee market research to identify emerging trends, customer needs, and competitor strategies.
- · Monitor client request modify or fixed code

Cebu Gems Innovation and Career Development Center Inc. May 2016 - Feb 2017 Front-end Admin

- Develop and maintain seafarer website.
- Monitor and maintain seafarer files.

REFERENCE

John Tiu

Network Engineer

Phone: 09176525933

Email:

Nikka Macachor

Q.A Web Tester

Phone: 09776127602

Email: nikkason123@gmail.com

Feb 2017 - Feb 2019